很好，你做完了。
Great.
You're done.
让我来展示我是如何做的。
Let me show you how I
implemented this one.
在DetailActivity文件的DetailFragment
里面。
Inside of detail fragment,
within detail activity.
首先，需要给loader加一个常量。
First, of course,
we add a constant for the loader.
同时需要加入一个projection ,用来存放我想要
从数据库里获取的列。
I've also added a projection for the
columns I want to get from the database.
当然，也需要是一个相对应的常量。
And, of course, corresponding constants.
这样我们的DetailFragment 里的
lorder 的 callback 就完成了。这个callback
Then we have our detail fragment
implement our loader callbacks for
是为cursor loader 准备的。
cursor loader.
当然，
这是一个参数化的cursor。
Of course,
with parametrized type cursor.
在 onCreate loader 函数里。
In on create loader.
我们创建一个新的cursor loader，
用来处理从intent来的URI。
We create a new cursor loader for
the URI that came in from the intent.
在 onLoadFinished, 需要我们来创建一个字符串
用来匹配在原先forecast
In onLoadFinished, I format a string to
match what was in the original forecast
fragment 并且用来把它们设置为mForecast
变量，就和TextView 一样。
fragment and set it to the mForecast
variable as well as the TextView.
对于onLoadrrRest 方法，并不需要
做什么改变。
We don't have to do anything
with onLoaderReset.
因为这里没有任何数据需要我们
暂时持有，直到我们需要把它们
Because there isn't any data that we
were holding onto that needs to be
清理掉。
cleaned up.
但是我们如何处理共享intent?
But, how do we fix the share intent?
首先要创建一个成员变量来
共享action provider。
I start by creating a member variable
for the share action provider.
这个变量是在onCreate 菜单
选项里设置的。
I set this variable in
on create options menu.
只有当我们有一个forecast的时候需要。
Only if we have a forecast.
我们不需要做任何关于
lorder发生顺序的设想。
We don't make any assumptions about
the order in which our loader happens.
最后在onLoadFinish 函数中，
把intent 设为 共享。
Finally in onload finish,
I set the share intent.
这样，程序会自动更新共享的action provider,
当它已经存在的时候。
This will update the share action
provider if it already exists.
让我们来确定这个依然可以工作。
Let's make sure this still works.
这些list 现在工作地跟我们期望的一样。
当我们点击其中一个。
The list as we would expect it to be and
when we click on one of these.
我们就跳转去detailView了。
We get the detail view.
我们还有一个共享action provider。
We even have a share action provider.
就和你看到的一样，我们能共享它，
这就是我们新的forecast。
And as you can see, we can share it,
and there's our forecast.